is preparing for this pit with Felipe Tito
he is a Shark tank
it's like studying for the test
is on
has a TCC
something in this sense
and now we have added the tall dome of Zé's brownie
what is this tramp here
the PC that is Zé's brownie front
and German here
o André
Charlie Brown
now screwed right brother
caraca now we have a meeting with Felipe Tito
and i need to get ready
this
idea Fábio is at Santos
preparing the tent
is with you Fábio
adhesive is already here
brownies are here
weeping bust is already here
all this for us to leave the tent beautiful
for guys to get there
come here i
We're back here with Charlie Brown's regular schedule.
eh the fair is really going on now
there in front of the
I'll be back here for the exchange of ideas
the partner talking shovel
business man born
man for man
for those who are calling me here now
and then I fall from the world
and then Juninho
I'm at a Charlie Brown Meeting
said Juninho
send 1 hug to my followers
1 hug there for all followers there
O we are together brother is us
Central South
Up in The West Side
California loves
California bug
Got your boy a King of Pug
i'm on One i Might develop in The Century
Club with my jeans on